fullscreensavers.com 2017-07-01

# Privacy Policy - FullScreensavers.com

**Collection and Use of your Personal Information**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

Any personal information that you provide to our web site shall stay absolutely safe, private, and secure. We do not resell personal information to outside sources. We may use your information to inform you about products or services offered by us and our partners. When placing an order, our e-commerce provider will handle your personal information and keep it absolutely safe, private and secure. In fact, even we cannot access your credit card information. 

This website uses Google Analytics and Google AdSense. You can find how Google uses data when you use this website: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>

**Security of your Personal Information**   
We have taken the appropriate steps and followed industry standards to secure any personal data stored by our systems. 

**Cookies**   
We may use cookies to store information about your visits to improve the use of our websites. In addition, during the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. We do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name and do not retrieve any information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. 

**IP Addresses**   
We may also collect your IP address for safety and security purposes. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. 

**Log Files**   
Other non-personal information collected in the form of logs - files that record website activity, including how many hits a particular web page is getting. This entries enable us to assess overall site activity, track interest in advertised sales, track interest in purchase behavior, and troubleshoot technical concerns. Through the use of log files, we may also collect certain demographic information such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), and the domain name of your Internet service provider. 

**Email Newsletter**   
Our newsletter is strictly run as an "opt-out" newsletter. We never send unsolicited emails. Information gathered during voluntary newsletter subscription is restricted to email address. This information is used solely by FullScreensavers.com and will not be sold to, or used by, any third party. We will only use this information for sending the regular newsletter about product updates and new releases. 

**Credit Card Transactions**   
We do not store any credit card information (name on credit card, credit card number and expiry date) for any purchase made on our site. 

**External Links**   
Our site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information. 

Your Choices You may unsubscribe from our e-mail list. You may direct us not to share your e-mail with our partners for offers of their products and services. You may also turn off cookies in your browser. 

**Contact Information**   
We welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you have questions about this Statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please please e-mail us using our contact webpage. By using this site, you signify your assent to the FullScreensavers.com Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes.   
You can contact us at
